<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="tinyos.yeti.debugger"
      label="Yeti 2 - TinyOS Debugger (optional)"
      version="1.2.16"
      provider-name="Silvan Nellen, ETH Zurich">

   <description url="http://tos-ide.ethz.ch/wiki/index.php">
      The TinyOS Debugger allows debugging applications on the nodes. This plugin requires the C Development Toolkit (CDT).
   </description>

   <copyright>
      [Enter Copyright Description here.]
   </copyright>

   <license>
      Copyright (c) 2008, ETH Zurich. All rights reserved.
Redistribution. 
Redistribution and use in binary form, without modification,
are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:
* Redistributions must reproduce the above copyright notice and
the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials
provided with the distribution.
* Neither the name of ETH Zurich nor the names of its suppliers
may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this
software without specific prior written permission.
* No reverse engineering, decompilation, or disassembly of this
software is permitted.
DISCLAIMER. 
THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS
&amp;quot;AS IS“ AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING,
BUT
NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT
SHALL THE COPYRIGHT OWNER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT,
INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES
(INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS
OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION)
HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT,
STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE)
ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED
OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="Yeti 2" url="http://tos-ide.ethz.ch/update/site.xml"/>
   </url>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.debug.core"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.filesystem"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.editors"/>
      <import feature="Feature_Core_Plugin" version="2.2.16"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.debug.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.workbench.texteditor"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.ide"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jface.text"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.cdt.debug.core"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.cdt.core"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.cdt.debug.mi.core"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.cdt.launch"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.cdt.ui"/>
      <import plugin="tinyos.yeti.core" version="2.2.16" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
   </requires>

  <includes id="tinyos.yeti.debugger.source" version="0.0.0" optional="true"/>
  
   <plugin
         id="tinyos.yeti.debugger"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
